[
  {
    "question": "Mars is the _________ planet from the sun.",
    "options": [
      "fifth",
      "fouth",
      "sixth"
    ],
    "correct": "fouth"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is the second _________planet in the solar system.",
    "options": [
      "smallest",
      "hottest",
      "coldest"
    ],
    "correct": "smallest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mars is named after the roman god of __________-.",
    "options": [
      "care",
      "love",
      "war"
    ],
    "correct": "war"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mars is called as the red planned due to its _____________.",
    "options": [
      "reddish appearance",
      "hotness",
      "red mud"
    ],
    "correct": "reddish appearance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mars atmospere is composed of _______.",
    "options": [
      "helium",
      "carbon dioxide",
      "silicon"
    ],
    "correct": "carbon dioxide"
  },
  {
    "question": "Equitorial diameter is about ____.",
    "options": [
      "<3000",
      "<5000",
      "<7000"
    ],
    "correct": "<7000"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mars has ___ number of moons.",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correct": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Orbit period is about ____.",
    "options": [
      "674",
      "687",
      "678"
    ],
    "correct": "687"
  },
  {
    "question": "Surface temperature is about ___.",
    "options": [
      "-153 to 30 c",
      "-153 to 20 c",
      "-153 to 10 c"
    ],
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Mars and ________ has  approximately the same landmass.",
    "options": [
      "mercury",
      "venus",
      "earth"
    ],
    "correct": "earth"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mars is home to the tallest mountain in the solar system calles as ____________-.",
    "options": [
      "olympus mons",
      "olampic mand",
      "olampad mons"
    ],
    "correct": "olympus mons"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many missions to mars have been successful?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "15",
      "18"
    ],
    "correct": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "On mars the moon of earth appears _________ the size from earth.",
    "options": [
      "half",
      "same",
      "three-fourth"
    ],
    "correct": "half"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mars has the largest _________ storm in the solar system.",
    "options": [
      "snow",
      "dust",
      "hail"
    ],
    "correct": "dust"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are signs of _________ on mars.",
    "options": [
      "life",
      "plants",
      "liquid"
    ],
    "correct": "liquid"
  }
]